[Music]
hey there this is bahader from
fabricator I'm so excited to announce
our newest feature the long-term demand
planning with this feature you will be
able to forecast your stores sales
revenue for the upcoming months this
will allow you to make better deals with
your suppliers and take the guess work
out of your planning you will decrease
your inventory and where house expenses
by keeping the ideal level of stock so
you will be able to save up some money
and invest it back in your Growing store
the demand planning has its own
challenges if you have tried it yourself
you know it but we leverage the most
modern technology out there to give you
the right answers we also keep in mind
that you are the one who is in the
driving seat which means you can edit
our forecasts and make it yours to see
how easily it is handled with our new
feature the let's get into the detail in
the next video I'll mention how you can
set up your forecasting just in a few
[Music]
clicks